for today's video we're going military
在今天的视频中，我们要去军队
let's look at how a tank works
让我们看看坦克是如何工作的
we're going to focus specifically on the American M1
我们将特别关注美国M1
A2 Abrams tank
A2艾布拉姆斯坦克
we'll look at the Caterpillar tracks the turret
我们看看毛毛虫在炮塔上留下的痕迹
where the crew sits
船员坐的地方
and the engine in the back that powers it all
后面的引擎为这一切提供动力
the M1 Abrams tank was introduced in the year 1980
M1艾布拉姆斯坦克于1980年推出
the tank was named in honor of United States Army
坦克是为了纪念美国陆军而命名的
general Creighton W
克雷顿将军
Abrams Jr who was a commander in the Vietnam War
小艾布拉姆斯是越南战争的指挥官
the idea with the M1
M1的想法
Abrams tank was to keep it low to the ground
艾布拉姆斯坦克是为了让它低到地面
so that it was harder to hit
这样就更难击中了
angled sides on the tank allow
水箱上的倾斜侧面允许
enemy fire to deflect off the side
使敌人的火力偏离一侧
it's a bit cozy inside
里面有点舒适
so I hope you're not claustrophobic
希望你没有幽闭恐惧症
during operations
在操作期间
the crew may spend hundreds of hours inside
船员们可能会在里面呆上几百个小时
with very little sleep
睡眠不足
there are many versions of the tank
坦克有很多版本
we have the M1 then came the M1 A1 and then the M1 A2
我们有M1，然后是M1 A1，然后是M1 A2
there's also minor variants of the tanks
坦克也有一些小的变体
with many different enhancement packages
有许多不同的增强包
but to keep things simple let's not worry about these
但是为了简单起见，我们不要担心这些。
just these three major versions
就这三个主要版本
they look very similar on the outside
它们外表看起来很相似
but there's been plenty of improvements to items
但是商品有很多改进。
such as the armor
比如盔甲
electronics and the weapons systems
电子和武器系统
each new version is generally heavier and slower
每个新版本一般都更重更慢
but the increased tech makes up for it
但增加的技术弥补了这一点
for the rest of the video
对于视频的其余部分
I'm going to focus specifically on the M1
我将特别关注M1。
A2 Abrams tank
A2艾布拉姆斯坦克
though some of what I'll say
虽然我要说的一些话
will be true of the previous versions as well
以前的版本也是如此
let's look at some specs
让我们看看一些规格
the height is 8 feet
高度是8英尺
the length is 32 feet
长度是32英尺
and the width is 12 feet
宽度是12英尺
for comparison here's the size of a person
作为比较，这里是一个人的大小
this tank weighs a whopping 68 US tons
这个坦克重达68吨
that's equal to the weight of about 35 cars
相当于35辆车的重量
even with all that weight
即使有那么大的重量
the tank is capable of speeds of
坦克的速度可达
up to 42 miles per hour
时速高达42英里
it has a fuel capacity of just under 500 gallons
它的燃料容量不到500加仑
again just for comparison most cars can only hold about
同样只是为了比较，大多数汽车只能容纳大约
16 gallons but tanks need all of that fuel
16加仑但油箱需要足够的燃料
because they only get about
因为他们只得到
6 miles per gallon compared to the average car
平均每加仑能跑6英里
25 miles per gallon
每加仑25英里
so it's a gas guzzler but it's heavy and powerful
所以这是一个耗油的车，但它又重又强大。
let's look at some of the features of the tank
让我们看看坦克的一些特点
we have the caterpillar tracks
我们找到了毛毛虫的足迹
the wheels there are seven on the ground on each side
轮子两边地上有七个
the main body which is called the hull
主体被称为船体
and the turret
还有炮塔
which is the part that spins on top
哪个是在上面旋转的部分
and holds the weapons and other equipment
并持有武器和其他设备
the engine is housed in the very back
引擎装在后面
the tank holds a crew of four
坦克上有四个船员
three of them are inside the turret
其中三个在炮塔里
and one of them is way up front
其中一个在前面
now that we're familiar with the outside of the tank
现在我们已经熟悉了水箱的外部
let's look at more specifics
让我们看看更多细节
and we'll start with the caterpillar tracks
我们从毛毛虫的足迹开始
these are sometimes called tank treads
这些有时被称为坦克踏板
they are made of steel with replaceable rubber pads
它们由钢制成，带有可更换的橡胶垫
there are seven road wheels on each side of the tank
坦克两边各有七个车轮
a raised idler wheel in the very front
前面有一个凸起的惰轮
and the drive sprocket in the back
还有后面的驱动链轮
this one has gear teeth on it
这个上面有齿轮齿
and it's the only one that's powered by the engine
它是唯一一个由引擎驱动的
it moves the entire track along
它沿着整个轨道移动
the other wheels spin freely
其他轮子自由旋转
as the tank treads move past it
当坦克驶过时
the road wheels also have suspension built into them
车轮也内置了悬架
the whole reason we use Caterpillar tracks
我们使用卡特彼勒轨道的全部原因
is to allow the tank to go over some
就是让水箱越过一些
very rough terrain
非常崎岖的地形
most barriers don't pose
大多数障碍不会构成
any problem for the tank to pass
坦克通过有什么问题吗？
regular vehicles with four wheels
四轮普通车辆
have limited surface area in contact with the ground
与地面接触的表面积有限
they can get stuck much easier
他们更容易卡住
that's why it's a good idea to stay on paved roads
这就是为什么呆在铺好的道路上是个好主意
the tank on the other hand
另一方面，坦克
has a much larger surface area
具有更大的表面积
to displace all of that weight
来转移所有的重量
obstacles in the way are usually not a problem
路上的障碍通常不是问题
the tank can even climb some very steep hills
坦克甚至可以爬上一些非常陡峭的山丘
most of the time
大多数时候
it's still a smooth ride for those inside the tank
对水箱里的人来说还是很顺利的
the tank is steered by altering the speed of the tracks
坦克通过改变履带的速度来转向
for example to turn left
例如向左转
the right tracks need to move faster
正确的轨道需要移动得更快
than the left tracks
比左边的轨道
unfortunately
不幸的是
the caterpillar tracks
毛毛虫追踪
are the most likely part of the tank to break
是水箱最有可能破裂的部分
the good news is
好消息是
that the tank usually carries tools and spare parts
坦克通常携带工具和备件
so that broken links can be replaced
以便可以更换损坏的链接
and the tank can keep moving again
坦克可以继续移动
next up is the engine
接下来是引擎
which is in the very back of the tank
它在水箱的最后面
for repairs
修理
the entire engine can be lifted up out of the tank
整个引擎可以从油箱里提出来
this is an AGT 1500 engine
这是一台AGT 1500发动机
which can run off of several different fuels
它可以使用几种不同的燃料
but most of the time it runs off of jet fuel
但大多数时候它会耗尽喷气燃料
in your car you'll find what's called a piston engine
在你的车里，你会发现所谓的活塞发动机
with these pistons moving up and down
随着这些活塞上下移动
to rotate the shaft
旋转轴
but in the tank you'll find a turbine engine
但是在油箱里你会发现一个涡轮发动机
this one works a little bit more like a jet engine
这个有点像喷气发动机
that you would find on an airplane
你会在飞机上找到
however this engine is actually fairly quiet
然而这个引擎实际上相当安静
which is really important
这真的很重要
so you don't give away the tanks
所以你不会放弃坦克
position to nearby enemies
对附近敌人的定位
the engine gets very hot
引擎变得很热
so
所以
these two side cooling units will help remove the heat
这两个侧面冷却单元将有助于去除热量
the exhaust comes out the back
排气从后面出来
so make sure and stay clear when the engine is on
所以引擎启动时一定要保持清醒
there's actually a phone on the back of the tank
水箱后面有电话
this way
这边走
soldiers on the outside can communicate with the crew
外面的士兵可以和船员交流
on the inside
在内部
the sides have armored plates called side skirts
侧面有称为侧裙的装甲板
to protect the wheels and the caterpillar tracks
来保护车轮和履带
these can be opened up in sections
这些可以分段打开
for better access to the road wheels
为了更好地接近车轮
on the front there's headlights here
前面有前灯
and four tow hooks down here
还有四个拖车钩
remember there are many different variants of the M1
请记住，M1有许多不同的变体
A2 Abrams tank
A2艾布拉姆斯坦克
so another tank might have slightly different features
所以另一个坦克可能有稍微不同的特征
on the outside
在外面
this top part is called the turret
这个顶部叫做炮塔
it can rotate all the way around in about nine seconds
它能在9秒内旋转一圈
this is the main gun
这是主炮
which is a 120 millimeter smoothbore cannon
这是一门120毫米滑膛炮
this means that the shells or ammunition are
这意味着炮弹或弹药是
120 millimeters
120毫米
and so is the bore or the hole that it goes through
孔或它穿过的孔也是如此
the shells leave the barrel
炮弹离开枪管
at about 3500 miles per hour
时速大约3500英里
it can hit a target two miles away
它能击中两英里外的目标
the automatic stabilizers
自动稳定器
allow the gun to stay locked on targets
让枪锁定目标
even while going over rough terrain
即使在崎岖的地形上
this way the driver doesn't have to stop
这样司机就不用停车了
every time the tank needs to fire
每次坦克需要开火的时候
the tank can even spin
坦克甚至可以旋转
in place while the main gun remains locked on target
在主炮锁定目标的同时就位
right next to this is the smaller coaxial machine gun
紧挨着这个的是较小的同轴机枪
up on top
在上面
there's usually at least one more machine gun
通常至少还有一挺机关枪
to operate on the sides are smoke grenade launchers
在侧面操作的是烟雾榴弹发射器
there's one on each side of the tank
水箱两边各有一个
these make it harder to be seen during combat
这使得在战斗中很难被看到
there's not much room for equipment inside of the tank
水箱里没有足够的空间放设备
so oftentimes
所以经常
the crew will put it out here on the bustle rack
工作人员会把它放在架子上
there are two hatches on top of the turret
炮塔顶部有两个舱门
the commander's hatch and the loader's hatch
指挥官舱口和装载机舱口
inside of the turret
炮塔内部
you'll find three out of the four crew members
你会发现四名船员中有三名
it's a bit cozy in here
这里有点舒适
the gunner sits down below to the very right
炮手坐在下面最右边
the commander sits directly behind the gunner
指挥官坐在炮手的正后方
the loader is off to the left of the main gun
装弹机在主炮左边
when the turret rotates
当炮塔旋转时
all three of these crew members rotate with it
这三个船员都跟着它旋转
underneath here this is called the turret basket
下面这个叫做炮塔篮
the seal between the turret and the hull is so good
炮塔和船体之间的密封太好了
that it could protect the crew inside
它可以保护里面的船员
in case of chemical
在化学的情况下
or nuclear warfare
或核战争
a few more things I want to show you about this tank
我还想给你看一些关于这个坦克的东西。
the commander can see 360 degrees around the tank
指挥官可以看到坦克周围360度
through the viewing ports
通过观看端口
the shells for the main gun
主炮的炮弹
are stored in a large compartment
储存在一个大隔间里
on the back of the turret
在炮塔的后面
the loader can then open up an access door
装载机可以打开一扇门
grab a shell and load the main gun
拿个炮弹装上主炮
this must be done quickly during combat situations
这必须在战斗中迅速完成
if any of the ammunition is ignited
如果任何弹药被点燃
the panels on top are rigged to blow off
顶部的面板被安装在爆炸处
so that the explosion goes up
这样爆炸就会上升
instead of into the turret where the crew is located
而不是进入船员所在的炮塔
the driver sits up at the very front
司机坐在最前面
there's a hatch up here that can be opened to go inside
上面有个舱门可以打开进去
there's not much room up here either
这里也没有多少空间
so the driver has to lay back in the seat
所以司机必须靠在座位上
the controls are up here and two brake pedals down here
控制器在上面两个刹车踏板在下面
there's no gas pedal in the tank
油箱里没有油门踏板
just use the two black handlebars
就用那两个黑色车把
for acceleration and steering
加速和转向
the driver also has periscopes
司机也有潜望镜
that allow him to see a 120 degree field of view
可以让他看到120度的视野
usually the driver enters through the hatch up front
通常司机从前面的舱门进去
but if needed the driver can climb into the turret
但如果需要，司机可以爬进炮塔
and then through a tiny door in the basket
然后穿过篮子里的一扇小门
and into the seat
并进入座位
The United States
美国
isn't the only ones to use the M1 Abrams tanks
不是唯一使用M1艾布拉姆斯坦克的
it's been sold to other countries such as Australia
它已经卖给了澳大利亚等其他国家。
Egypt Kuwait and Saudi Arabia
埃及科威特和沙特阿拉伯
the M1
M1
A2 Abrams tank has been in use for almost 30 years now
A2艾布拉姆斯坦克已经使用了将近30年了
at some point it may be replaced
在某个时候它可能会被替换
but for now it continues to be the main battle tank
但目前它仍然是主战坦克
for the United States military
对美国军方来说
my name's Jared and I create
我叫贾里德，我创造
3d animations on how things work
关于事物如何工作的3d动画
visit my YouTube channel
访问我的YouTube频道
for lots more animations just like this one
对于更多像这样的动画
go ahead and click on the link here
继续并单击此处的链接
or click below to watch another video
或点击下方观看其他视频
and thanks again to War Thunder
再次感谢战雷
download the game for free
免费下载游戏
just use my link in the video description below
只需在下面的视频描述中使用我的链接